

# **Md Mozammil**

Full stack designer



#### **ADDRESS**

A49 Kilokary Maharani Bagh new delhi - 110014



#### CONTACT

Phone

+91-9540401978

Email

mozammil.babu@gmail.com

# **CONNECT ME ON**



linkedin.com/in/mdmozammil/



instagram.com/mohdmozammil/



twitter.com/MozammilBabu

## **PORTFOLIO LINKS**

www.mdmozammil.com
www.behance.net/MOZAMMIL

#### **SUMMARY**

Design anything.

I'm a full stack designer based out of Delhi, India with over 8+ years of experience. I specialize in creating clean, minimal and aesthetic design aiming towards solving the need of the target audience. Designing is not just my job but passion, my goal is to create an easily accessible user interface.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Sociowash | From Oct 2017 Present

Senior UX Designer

MakeMyTrip.com | From Aug 2016 to Sep 2017

Senior Executive user experience

Repindia.com | From Sep 2015 to July 2016

**UX** Designer

Snapdeal.com | From April 2013 to Sep 2015

Senior Graphic Designer

Lenskart.com | From May 2011 to April 2013

Graphic Designer

## **EDUCATION**

Diploma | 2010 to 2013

Diploma in Graphic & Web Design form Arena Animation

Collage | 2010 to 2013

Graduate in bachelor of science

# TOOLS SKILL Photoshop Illustrator Adobe XD Premiere SKILL Website Design Graphic Design Visualise App Design

# **INTERESTS**



Cricket





Travel

Music